Annika Lundberg

CV



Email: annikalundberg97@gmail.com Phone: +46 73 633 20 37

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/annikalundberg97

I'm a motivated 24 years old from Sweden who loves design and programming. I have previously worked in IT and been part of different student organisations. In the future I dream about working with web development while making the world a better place.

Experience

Frontend Developer

Aug 2019 - Now

Portfolio: www.thecreativegoose.com

We Know IT, Linköping, Sweden

- Responsible for web design and implementation
- Independent responsibility for dialog with client
- Working with several projects at the same time

Web Designer (internship)

Aug 2018 - Dec 2018

Kreativ-kraft, Linköping, Sweden

- Got the internship by own in initiative
- Used marketing tools and implemented SEO
- Created content to websites, took photos and wrote texts

Education

Bachelor in Cognitive Science

Aug 2018 - Jun 2021

Linköping University, Sweden

- Studying my third and last year
- Courses in web development, interaction design and programming
- Learnt HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP

Eberhard Karls University of Tübingen

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

Tübingen, Germany

- Erasmus exchange for one semester
- Studying courses in philosophy, history and german

Professional Affiliations

Welcome Period- and Activity Committee Coordinator

May 2019 - May 2020

ESN Linköping, Linköping University

- Organized events for 500 Erasmus students
- Planned and organized over 30 events
- Increased the participants from previous years
- Established relations with different associations on campus
- Responsible for a committee

Marketing responsible

Jun 2018 - Jun 2019

Linköping Vegan Association, Linköping University

- Responsible for all marketing on social media
- Created a new website with HTML and CSS
- Increased the followers on Facebook with 40 %

References

References available upon request